Guide to the Clarence Bloomfield Moore collection, 1891-1918.
Moore, Clarence Bloomfield collection, 1891-1918
- Series I. Field Notebooks
  - Notebook # 14, 1897-1898 (Box 1)
    Small notebook. 68p. South Carolina, Savannah River, and Altahama. Beginning entry, Indian Hill, undated. p.1-68. Includes the following sites in South Carolina and Georgia sites in Beaufort, Chatham, Screven, Barnwell, Liberty (South Carolina and Georgia), Wayne, Tatnall, and Appling counties:
    South Carolina: Bluffton (Cressons), Burton Hill, Port Royal Island, Calawassie Island, Hasell Point, Indian Hill, Indian Hill, St. Helena Island, Little Island, Polleewahnee Island.
    Savannah River: Brooks Landing, Hudson's Ferry, Mills Landing, Pipe Makers Creek.
    Altahama River: Beards Bluff, Buckhorn Bluff, Darien, Gray's Landing, Hell's Shoals, Iron Mine, Joiner's Island, Lake Bluff, Matlock's Water Pond, Mitchell's Lake, Old River, Reddish Landing, Tilman's Ferry.
  - Notebook # 15, 1899 (Box 1)
    Small notebook. 155p. Mobile River, Alabama. Entries begin with February 8, 1899, p.1-85. Expedition accounts, p.86-94, 154-155. Includes the following sites in Mobile, Wilcox, Montgomery, Dallas, Monroe, and Elmore counties:
    Alabama River, Big Eddy Landing, Burford's Landing, Charlotte Thompson's Place, Coal Bluff, Coosa River, Durand's Bend, Horseshoe Bend, Hunter Place, Jackson's Bend, Little River Mound, Little River, Matthew's Landing, Matthew's Place, Potts Landing, Taloosa and Coosa River, Twenty-one Mile Landing, Webb's Landing.
  - Notebook # 16, 1899 (Box 1)
    Large notebook. 200p. Alabama and Mobile Rivers. Includes sites in Wilcox, Montgomery, Elmore, Dallas, and Monroe counties. Beginning entry, Twenty-one Mile Bluff, undated. p.11- 108. Accounting entries p.111-115. Includes journal entries February 6, 1899-April 22, 1899, p.183-200.
  - Notebook # 17, 1900 (Box 1)
    Large notebook. 202p. Florida west coast. Includes sites in Hillsboro, Lee, Monroe, and Manatee counties. Beginning entry, mound near Riverview, undated. p.1-47. Includes journal entries January 12, 1900-April 27, 1900, p.178-202.
    Also available on Reel 3
  - Notebook # 18, 1901 (Box 2)
    Small notebook. 134p. Northwest coast of Florida, Alabama, and Mississippi. Beginning entry, Butler's Gin, undated. p.1-134. Includes the following sites in Marengo, Baldwin, Pickens, Greene, and Sumter counties, Alabama; Washington, Santa Rosa, and Walton counties, Florida; and Pickens and Lowndes counties, Mississippi:
    Alabama: Bear Point, Birkley's Landing, Blubber Creek, Bryan's Barn, Goose Pond, Kirkpatrick's Landing, Moscon, Simmon's Landing, Spragin's Mill, Sucarnoochee Creek, Summerville.
    Florida: Basin Bayou, Black Creek, Camp Walton, Choctawhatchee Bay, Don's Bayou, Freeport, Graveyard Point, Jolly B, Maesta Creek, Point Washington.
    Mississippi: Butler's Gin, Chowder Spring, Columbus, Crawford, Wyndham Landing.
  - Notebook # 19, 1901 (Box 2)
    Large notebook. 251p. Tombigbee River, Mississippi and Alabama. Includes sites in Lowndes, Pickens, Greene, Sumter, Marengo, Baldwin, Santa Rosa, Walton, and Washington counties. Pages of possible site locations, through p.10. Beginning entry, mound at Butler's Gin, undated. p.22-126. Correspondence attached p.252-253. Includes journal entries January 16, 1901- April 25, 1901, p.232-251.
  - Notebook # 20, 1902 (Box 2)
    Large notebook. 299p. Northwest coast of Florida. Includes sites in Franklin, Cahoun, Washington, Lafayette, Levy, Wakulla, and Taylor counties. Pages of possible site locations through p.2. Beginning entry, Cool Spring Mound, undated. p.8- 230. Enclosures. Includes journal entries January 14, 1902-May 13, 1902, p.276-299.
  - Notebook # 21, 1902 (Box 2)
    Small notebook. 110p. Entries p.1-110. Northwest coast of Florida. Includes the following sites in Franklin, Wakulla, Taylor, Lafayette, and Levy counties:
    Aucilla River, Econfenne River, Goodson's Fish Camp, Horseshoe Point, Mound Field, Murphy's Landing, Nichols Mound, Ocklockonee Bay, Pine Key, Shell Heap, Spring Creek, Steinhatchee River, Warrior River, Yent Mound.
  - Notebook # 22, 1902 (Box 2)
    Small notebook. 176p. Apalachicola River, northwest Florida. Beginning entry, Cool Spring Mound, undated. p.1-176. Includes the following sites in Franklin, Bay, and Calhoun counties:
    Alligator Bayon, Anderson's Bayou, Apalachiocola, Baker's Landing, Bear Point, Burnt Mill Creek, Carabelle R. Mound, Cool Springs Mound, Davis Point, Eleven-mile Point, Gotier Hammock, Green's Point, Hare Hammock, Holley Mound, Huckleberry Landing, Indian Pass Point, Jackson Mound, Laughton's Bayou, Magnolia Cemetry, Pearl Bayou, Pierce Mound, Singer Mound, Sowell Mound, Strange's Landing, Tucker Mound.
  - Notebook # 23, 1903 (Box 2)
    Small notebook. 146p. Suwannee River, Apalachicola River, and Gulf Coast, Florida. Entries begin with mound near the Brickyard. p.1-146. Includes the following sites in Levy, Lafayette, Liberty, Calhoun, Gadsden, Jackson, Hernando, Pasco, Hillsboro, and Citrus counties:
    Suwanee River: Fannings, Fayettesville, Fowler's Landing, Jenning's Landing, Rocky Landing.
    Chipola River: Burgess Center, Chipola Cut-off, Isabel Landing. Apalchicola River: Aspalga, Atkins Landing, Blountstown, Brickyard Center, Bristol, Chattahoochee Landing, Davis Field, Estiffanulga, Sampson's Landing, Yon Mound.
    Gulf Coast: Bayport, Bear Landing, Cedar Keys, Chassahowitzka River, Clear Water, Crystal River, Dry Creek, Gigger Point, Hog Island, Indian Bend, Indian Creek, John's Pass, Long Key, Pichlochascootie River, Rock Island, Wekiwachee River.
  - Notebook # 24, 1903 (Box 2)
    Large notebook. 300p. Suwannee River and Apalachicola Rivers, Florida. Includes sites in Franklin, Calhoun, Liberty, Gadsden, Jackson, Lafayette, Levy, Hillsboro, Citrus, Hernando, and Pasco counties. Notes and listing of possible sites through p.3. Entries begin with mound on Brickyard Creek. p.11-132. Includes journal entries January 13, 1903-April 18, 1903. p.281- 300.
    Also available on Reel 4
  - Notebook # 25, 1904-1906 (Box 2)
    Large notebook. 300p. Florida, Mississippi, Alabama. Includes sites in Hale, Greene, Tuscaloosa, Clark, Washington, Choctaw, Marengo, Baldwin, and Mobile counties, Alabama; Jackson county, Mississippi; and Osceola, DeSoto, and Lee counties, Florida. Entries begin with Lauier mound. p.9-199. Includes journal entries, January 11, 1904-April 21, 1904; December 29, 1904-April 25, 1905; January 25, 1906-April 18, 1906. p.249-300.
  - Notebook # 26, 1905 (Box 2)
    Small notebook. 181p. Lake Tohopekaliga, and Charlotte Harbor, Florida; Mobile Bay, Alabama; Mississippi Sound, Mississippi; Lower Tombigbee, Alabama. Entries begin January 11, 1905. p.1-181. Includes the following sites in Osceola and Lee counties, Florida; Baldwin, Choctaw, Marengo, Hale, Greene, Tuscaloosa, Clark, and Washington counties, Alabama; and Jackson and Harrison counties, Mississippi:
    Lake Tohopekaliga and Charlotte Harbor: Brown's Landing, Frier Cove, Kissimmee, Lanier Mound, Lee's Landing, McCool's Landing, Pine Island, Punta Rassa, St. Elmo Landing.
    Mobile Bay and Simpson Island: Blakeley's, Bon Secours River, Bottle Creek, Fish River, Seymour Bluff, Starke's Wharf, Strong's Bayou.
    Lower Tombigbee: Baska Creek, Bass Landing, Beaver's Creek, Breckenridge Landing, Carney's Bluff, Cox Landing, Cut-off, Gaines Landing, Hook's Plantation, Horse Creek, Jackson's Landing, Kimbell's Field, Malone's Gin, Payne's Woodyard, Peavey's Landing, Powe's Landing, Rembert, Santa Bogue, Steiner's Landing, Three River Landing, Walter's Plant.
    Black Warrior: Arcola, Bohannon's Landing, Calvin's Landing, Candy's Landing, Lock No.7, McAlpin's Woodyard, Moundville, Stephen's Bluff.
  - Notebook # 27, 1905 (Box 2)
    . Small notebook. 77p. Flint River, Chattahoochee River, and Moundville. Entries p.1-77. Includes the following sites in Decatur, Clay, and Quitmon counties, Georgia; Jackson county, Florida, and Early, Houston, Henry, and Russell counties, Alabama:
    Flint River: Kerr's Landing, Log Landing, Munnerlyn's Landing.
    Chattahoochee River: Abercrombie Landing, Columbia, Fort Gaines, Fullmore's Upper Landing, Georgetown, Hare's Landing, Kemp's Landing Old Rambo Landing Purcell's Landing, Shoemaker Landing, Starke's Clay Landing, Steammill Landing.
  - Notebook # 28, 1906 (Box 2)
    Small notebook. 88p. Moundville Revisited. Crystal River. Entries begin with Crystal River revisited. p.1-88.
  - Notebook # 29, 1905-1906 (Box 2)
    Large Notebook. 252p. Chattahoochee River and Flint River. Includes sites in Jackson county, Florida; Decatur, Early, Clay, Quitman, Chattahoochee, Russell, and Muscogee counties, Georgia; and Houston, Henry, and Barbour counties, Alabama. Entries begin with mound near Kerr's Landing. p.5-62. Includes journal entries November 7, 1905-December 10, 1905, p.246-252.
    Also available on Reel4
  - Notebook # 30, 1907-1908 (Box 2)
    Large notebook. 198p. Yazoo, Sunflower, and Arkansas Rivers. Includes sites in Washington, Warren, Issaquenna, Sharkey, Yazoo, Holmes, and Leflore counties, Mississippi; and Arkansas, Jefferson, and Lincoln counties, Arkansas. Entries begin with Blum mounds. p.1-112. Includes journal entries January 13, 1907-April 19, 1908, p.146-198.
  - Notebook # 31, 1908-1909 (Box 2)
    Large notebook. 198p. Ouachita Valley, Little River, Bayou Bartholomew. Includes sites in Catahoula, Caldwell, Ouachita, Grant, Franklin, and Morehouse parishes, Louisiana; and Ashley, Bradley, Union, and Calhoun counties, Arkansas. Entries begin November 18, 1908. p.7-165. Includes journal entries November 6, 1908-April 26, 1909, p.171-198.
  - Notebook # 32, 1908 (Box 2)
    Small notebook. 163p. Mississippi and Arkansas. Entries begin with Blum Mounds. p.1-163. Includes the following sites in Sharkey, Yazoo, Holmes, Washington, Leflore, Issaquenna, and Warren counties, Mississippi; Arkansas, Lincoln, and Jefferson counties, Arkansas:
    Sunflower River: Anderson Landing, Bachelor Retreat, Blum Mounds, Fairview Landing, Fairview Plantation, George Lake, Spanish Fort Landing, Stalonia Landing, Wrong-end-up Landing.
    Yazoo River: Belzona, Carey Middleton Gin Landing, Caruthers Landing, Clark's Ferry, Fort Place, Hayne's Bluff, Honey Island, King's Crossing, Koalunsa, Leist Landing, Monterey, O'Neill's Landing, Parker's Bayou, Silent Shade Landing, Stella, Tchula Lake, Wasp Lake, Welsh Camp Landing, Yalobusha River.
    Arkansas River: Douglas, Greer, Menard Mounds, Old River Landing, Sawyer's Landing.
  - Notebook # 33, 1909-1910 (Box 2)
    Small notebook. 151p. White River, Black River, and St. Francis River, Arkansas. Entries begin with mound near Mt. Adams. p.1-151. Includes the following sites in Prairie, Arkansas, White, Woodruff, Jackson, Lawrence, Randolph, Lee, St. Francis, Independence, Cross, and Poinsett counties:
    White River: Atkinson Ferry, Chandler Landing, Hames Place, King's Landing, Lindsay's Point, Mt. Adams, Negro Hill, Taylor's Bayou, Teague Mound.
    Black River: Clover Bend, Cornpen Landing, Elgin, Harter Knoll, Lauratown, Lindley Landing, Little Turkey Hill, Mitchell's Log Camp Landing, Perkins Field, Tucker Bay, Upper Hovey Place.
    St. Francis River: Bay Ferry, Big Eddy, Castile Place, Catfish Mounds, Cummings Place, Forrest Place, Fortune Mounds, Miller Place, Neeley's Ferry, Parkin's, Potter Place, Rose Mound, Stott Place, Togo, Turkey Island, Turnbow Place, Whitehall Place.
    Also available on Reel 5
  - Notebook # 34, 1910-1911 (Box 2)
    . Small notebook. 134p. Mississippi River. Entries begin November 10, 1910, p.1-134. Includes the following sites in Mississippi, Crittenden, Lee, Tunica, Phillye's, Bolivar, Desha, Washington, and Warren counties; and Concordia and Pointe Coupee parishes:
    Middle Mississippi Valley: Avenue, Bradley, Commerce, Kent Place, Mount Place, Pecan Point, Rhodes, Stoffle Place.
    Lower Mississippi Valley: Glass, Glendale, Nebletts, Oak Bend, Richland, Shadyside Landing, Shaw Fields.
  - Notebook # 35, 1909-1910 (Box 2)
    . Large notebook. 200p. St. Frances River, White River, Black River, Arkansas. Includes sites in Lee, St. Francis, Poinsett, Monroe, Arkansas, Prairie, White, Woodruff, Jackson, Independence, Lawrence, and Randolph counties. Enclosure lists counties in Alabama, Florida, and Mississippi. Entries begin with White River. p.7-133. Includes journal entries November 9, 1909-April 25, 1910, p.178-200.
  - Notebook # 36, 1910-1911 (Box 3)
    Large notebook. 200p. Mississippi River Valley, Lower Mississippi, Red River. Includes sites in Phillips, Lee, Crittenden, Mississippi, and Desha counties, Arkansas; Tunica, Adams, Bolevar, and Washington counties, Mississippi; and Pointe Coupee and Avoyelles parishes, Louisiana. Entries begin March 21, 1911. p.7-127. Includes journal entries November 7, 1910- April 24, 1911, p.177-200.
  - Notebook # 37, 1911-1912 (Box 3)
    Large notebook. 200p. Red River, Arkansas and Louisiana. Includes sites in Miller, Lafayette, Hempstead, and Bowie counties, Arkansas; Pointe Coupee, Avoyelles, Rapides, Grant, Red River, Bossier, and Caddo parishes, Louisiana. Entries begin with notes. p.7-174. Includes journal entries November 6, 1911-April 26, 1912, p.177-200.
  - Notebook # 38, 1911-1912 (Box 3)
    Small notebook. 179p. Red River. Entries begin with Keller Place. p.1-118. Sketch on p.179. Includes the following sites in Pointe Coupee, Avoyelle, Rapides, Grant, Red River, and Bossier parishes, Louisiana; and Miller, Lafayette, and Hempsted counties, Arkansas:
    Red River: Battle's, Briar Bend, Byram Ferry, Crenshaw, Diggs Bluff, Dooley Ferry, Dunn's, Fosters, Fridays, Gahagan, Haley's, Haynes, Johnson's, Keller Place, L'Eau Noire Bayou, Lacroix, Mayer's, McClure's Place, Moore's, Norman Landing, Saline Point, Sulphur River, Taylortown, Thompson's.
  - Notebook # 39, 1912-1913 (Box 3)
    Small notebook. 180p. Ouachita Valley, Louisiana and Saline River, Arkansas. Entries begin with Pritchard's Landing. p.1-85; p.180 has continuation. Includes the following sites in Catahoula, Tensas, West Carroll, East, Franklin, Madison, and Louisiana parishes; and Bradley county, Arkansas:
    Ouachita Valley: Alphenia Place, Crowfoot Place, Dean Lake, Flynn's Place, Hope Landing, Insley Place, Jackson's Place, Lake Place, Lower Jackson Place, Montgomery, Motley Place, Mott Place, Poverty Point, Pritchard's Landing, Richardson Place, Stevens, Turkey Point Landing.
    Saline River: Brooks Landing, Godfrey Landing, Goulett Island, Hampton landing, Lowrie Landing, Moore's Mill, Wherry's Landing, Wire Fence Landing.
  - Notebook # 40, 1912-1913 (Box 3)
    Large notebook. 200p. Saline River, Arkansas; Bayou d'Arbonne, Atchafalaya River, and Tensas River, Louisiana. Includes sites in Ashley and Bradley counties, Arkansas; and Union, Assumption, Ibeia, Iberville, St. Landry, Concordia, Catahoula, Tensa, Madison, Franklin, East Carroll, and West Carroll parishes, Louisiana. Entries begin with Goulett Island. p.9-158. Includes journal entries November 9, 1912-April 23, 1913, p.174-200.
  - Notebook # 41, 1913-1914 (Box 3)
    Large notebook. 298p. Tennessee River, Eastern Tennessee, Mississippi and Alabama. Includes sites in Hamilton, James, Meigs, Rhea, Roane, Loudon, Blount, Knox, Livingston, Lyon, Marshall, Stewart, Henry, Benton, Humphrey, Decatur, Wayne, and Hardin counties, Tennessee; Tishomingo county, Mississippi; and Lauderdale and Colbert counties, Alabama. Tennessee River entries p.7-238. Includes journal entries November 3, 1913-April 29, 1914, p.268-298.
    Also available on Reel 6
  - Notebook # 42, 1914 (Box 3)
    Small notebook. 101p. Entries p.1-101. Includes the following sites in Rhea, Meigs, Loudon, Blount, Knox, Roane, Stewart, Henry, Benton, Wayne, Hardin, Harniston, Hamilton, and James counties, Tennessee; and Marshall county, Kentucky:
    Tennessee River: Arthur Place, Barrett's Ferry, Beech Creek, Bess Place, Citico Mound, Cooks Landing, Dickey Place, Eldridge Place, Evan's Place, Gray's Place, Henson, Hiwassee Island, Hodds Ferry, Hoyal Ferry, Huffine Ferry, Igou Ferry, Jackson Place, Johnson Creek, Jones Place, Koger Island, Little River Shoals, Lovelady Landing, North Carolina Landing, Perkins Bluff, Shipps Landing, Sykes Place, Thompson, Wolf Island.
  - Notebook # 43, 1914-1915 (Box 3)
    Large notebook. 300p. Tennessee River. Includes sites in Stewart, Humphreys, Benton, Marion, and Hamilton counties, Tennessee; and Decatur, Lauderdale, Colbert, Lawrence, Limestone, Morgan, Alabama, Marshall, and Jackson counties, Alabama. Notes p.7. Entries p.9-273. Includes journal entries November 4, 1914-April 28, 1915, p.275-300.
  - Notebook # 44, 1914-1915 (Box 3)
    Small notebook. 148p. Citico revisited, Tennessee. Includes Citico mound and Williams Landing, Hamilton County, Tennessee. Index, p.1. Entries p.3-148.
  - Notebook # 45, 1915-1918 (Box 3)
    Large notebook. 300p. Ohio River, Green River, Mississippi River. Includes sites in Ballard, Livingston, Henderson, McLean, Ohio, Butler, Edmonson. Fulton, and Hickman counties, Kentucky; Massac and Pope counties, Illinois; Posey county, Indiana; Lauderdale county, Tennessee; New Madrid and Mississippi counties, Missouri. Notes, p.7. Entries p.9-208. Includes journal entries November 4, 1915-April 26, 1916; November 8, 1916-April 23, 1917; September 25, 1917- April 26, 1918, p.218-300.
- Series II. Other Material
  - Printed guide and Catalogue (Box 1)
  - Unnumbered notebook., 1891 (Box 3)
    Contains Cruise of the Osceola, p.1-77. Entries from January 21-February 23, 1891. Cruise of the Alligator. Entries from March 5-April 7, 1891, p.79-99. Journal entries describe boat trips in Florida investigating potential archaeological sites.
  - Dictionary of Archaeological Terms. (Box 3)
    240p. Includes alphabetical index of archaeological terms, with page references. p.3-91. Terms are then defined. Includes bibliographic citations. p.108-126. Notes on various books, p.224-240
  - Correspondence., 1899 (Box 3)
    1899 correspondence from George W. Rossignol to Clarence B. Moore. Often addressed to Dr. M.G. Miller. About a proposed expedition to the Coosa River in Alabama and Georgia. May 17, 1899-August 1, 1899. Undated letters at end.
- Series III. Guide to Notebooks by Year
  Notebook # - - - - -
  Years Covered
  1
  1891
  2
  1892
  3
  4
  1892-1893
  5
  1893-1894
  6
  7
  1894
  8
  1894-1895
  9
  10
  1895-1896
  11
  1896-1897
  12
  13
  1897-1898
  14
  15
  1899
  16
  17
  1900
  18
  1901
  19
  20
  1902
  21
  22
  23
  1903
  24
  25
  1904-1906
  26
  1905
  27
  28
  1906
  29
  1905-1906
  30
  1907-1908
  31
  1908-1909
  32
  33
  1909-1910
  34
  1910-1911
  35
  36
  37
  1911-1912
  38
  39
  1912-1913
  40
  41
  1913-1914
  42
  1914
  43
  1914-1915
  44
  45
  1915-1918
- Series IV. Guide to Notebooks by Location
  - Alabama
    County - - - - -
    Notebook #
    Baldwin
    18, 25, 26
    Barbour
    Choctaw
    25, 26
    Clark
    Colbert
    Dallas
    15, 16
    Decatur
    Elmore
    Greene
    18, 19, 25, 26
    Hale
    25, 26, 28, 29
    Henry
    27, 29
    Houston
    Jackson
    Lauderdale
    Lawrence
    Limestone
    Madison
    Marengo
    Marshall
    Mobile
    Monroe
    Montgomery
    Morgan
    Pickens
    18, 19
    Russell
    Sumter
    Tuscaloosa
    Washington
    25, 36
    Wilcox
  - Arkansas
    Arkansas
    30, 32, 33, 35
    Ashley
    31, 40
    Bowie
    Bradley
    31, 39, 40
    Calhoun
    Crittenden
    34, 36
    Cross
    33, 35
    Desha
    Hempstead
    37, 38
    Independence
    Jefferson
    30, 32
    Lafayette
    Lee
    33, 34, 35, 36
    Lincoln
    Miller
    Mississippi
    Phillips
    Poinsett
    Prairie
    Randolph
    St. Francis
    Union
    White
    Woodruff
  - Florida
    Bay
    Brevard
    1, 2, 3
    20, 22, 23, 24
    Citrus
    21, 324
    Clay
    5, 6
    Duval
    5, 6, 8, 9
    Franklin
    20, 21, 22, 23, 24
    Gadsden
    23, 24
    Hernando
    Hillsboro
    17, 23, 24
    23, 24, 27, 29
    20, 21, 23, 24
    Lake
    1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
    17, 26
    Levy
    Liberty
    Manatee
    Marion
    6, 8, 9
    Orange
    1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 7
    Osceola
    Pasco
    Putnam
    1, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9
    St. Johns
    Santa Rosa
    Taylor
    20, 21
    Volusia
    1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7
    Wakulla
    Walton
    18, 19, 20, 22
  - Georgia
    Appling
    13, 14
    Belleville
    Bryan
    11, 12
    Camden
    Chatham
    12, 13, 14
    Chattahochee
    Decautur
    Early
    11, 12, 13, 14
    McIntosh
    10, 11, 12
    Muscogee
    Quitman
    Screven
    Stewart
    Tattnall
    Wayne
  - Illinois
    Massac
    Pope
  - Indiana
    Posey
  - Kentucky
    Ballard
    Butler
    Edmonson
    Fulton
    Henderson
    Hickman
    Livingston
    McLean
    Ohio
  - Louisiana
    Parish - - - - -
    Assumption
    Avoyelles
    36, 37, 38
    Bossier
    Caddo
    Caldwell
    Catahoula
    Concordia
    34, 36, 40
    East Carroll
    39, 40
    Grant
    31, 37, 38
    Iberia
    Iberville
    Morehouse
    Ouachita
    Pointe Coupee
    34, 36, 37, 38
    Rapides
    Red River
    St. Landry
    Tensas
    West Carroll
    West Feliciana
  - Mississippi
    Adams
    Bolivar
    Harrison
    Holmes
    Issaquena
    Leflore
    Lowndes
    Sharkey
    Tunica
    Warren
    30, 34, 36
    30, 32, 36
    Yazoo
  - Missouri
    New Madrid
  - South Carolina
    Barnwell
    Beaufort
    Burke
  - Tennessee
    Benton
    42, 43
    Blount
    41, 42
    Dyer
    Hamilton
    41, 42, 43, 44
    Hardin
    Humphreys
    James
    Knox
    Loudon
    Meig
    Rhea
    Roane